[Music]
Hello friends, I am Manish Arora
from Investments and have brought with me
a health insurance policy
called ICC Health Advantage Policy. This is a
very good policy. Friends, ICC has
revised this policy a lot and has
added many extra features to it. So let's start ICC Health
Advantage Policy. So let's discuss
some of the features of ICC Health Advantage Policy.
Its entry is 18 years. Friends, a
person between 18 years to 65 years can
enroll in this policy. You can buy this policy
individually for yourself and for your family.
This policy can be
bought in individual form as well as
in family floater.
In family floater, you
can also add your wife and your children.
Friends, the sub-insured of this policy is
minimum 5 lakhs and up to 3 crores. You
can buy this policy. The
IT coverage in this policy is for a minimum of 5
lakhs and up to 3 crores. Friends, you can get coverage of minimum 5 lakhs and up to 3 crores.
Friends,
you can pay the premium of this policy for one year, two years and
three years.  You can pay it friends, it
means if you pay the premium of this policy for 2 years
together and pay the premium for 3 years
together, then the company
gives you some discount
for paying the premium in full, that is, you get an extra discount on the premiums of 2 years and 3 years,
friends, there is no
room rent capping in this policy, friends,
if there is any kind of hospital and you pay the
room rent of that hospital for ₹ 10000, 15000, there is a
suite room, there is a superior deluxe room, you
can take any room, friends, in this
no room rent capping, in this way, in this no room rent capping
also, whatever charges there are in ICU, the
company removes them and the
company pays for it, so
you will not have to pay any extra charge for ICU also,
friends, apart from this, post hospital
means if any claim comes,
friends, the seven days before that and post
hospital means friends, any
medical checkups or tests for up to 180 days after the claim are
done in this policy, friends, so you  Normally
people ask us
how can we avail the benefits of this full hospital coverage. You
can avail it only through reimbursement.
For that, you have to pay the bills. Friends, whatever
expenses you have incurred before admission
and after hospital discharge,
you will pay them. After submitting all those bills,
you will fill the reimbursement form and
submit it to the company and the company will
also give you that money. Friends, now let us know
when can you take a claim.
In this policy, you can claim after 30 days.
After 30 days, you can take any kind of claim.
Except accidental, the claim will
start from the first day and
apart from that, any other claim that you
take in this policy, friends, will
start after 30 days. But it also has some conditions
like pre-existing disease. If you or
your family member has any kind of
existing disease and you have
mentioned it while taking the policy, then its coverage is for
24 months.  This policy starts after a year.
This is a very good benefit in
this policy. Friends, normally in other
policies, in some policies, this coverage starts after 36
months, in some policies, this existing
coverage starts after 48 months, three years or four years.
Friends, but in this policy,
your full
visiting coverage starts after 24 months, friends.
Apart from this, there are some specified diseases whose
coverage starts only after 24 months
because IIT considers those diseases to be
slow-moving diseases which
spread slowly. Their coverage will
start after 24 months and there is a list of them
because it is given in our description box.
You can see it in the policy wording.
I will give you some examples of it,
friends, like hernia,
uterus removal, cataract, prostate, these are some
diseases whose coverage will
start only after 24 months. You
can see this list in the description box below.
Friends, apart from this, in this policy, friends, the
care treatments which are covered are
covered.  Friends, what does this policy
mean, it is advancement, it is
technology advancement. There are some diseases
which can be treated with these 24 hours
and the
patient does not have the retirement of 24-hour hospital facilities.
Friends, so it means that
some diseases which do not require 24-hour
hospitalization, that coverage
is also available in this policy. Friends, apart from the
care treatments that are covered in this policy, you also
get Nucleic Bonus, a granted no-claim bonus,
which is up to 100%. I will
tell you this with an example, friends, but for example,
if you take a policy of Rs 10 lakh, then
you will keep getting 20% ​​no-claim bonus every year till the next five years. That means,
if you take a policy of Rs 10 lakh, then every year
20%, that is, Rs 2 lakh no-claim bonus will keep getting added
to your policy with the
premium. So, it means your policy will increase from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 12 lakh,
then Rs 14 lakh, then Rs 16 lakh, then Rs 18 lakh, then
in the fifth year your policy will be of Rs 20 lakh.  If the sum assured
becomes 20 lakhs, then friends, you get 100% no claim
bonus in this policy
because it is a very good no claim bonus
feature, friends, apart from this, friends, you get
every family health checkup in this policy,
health checkup which is 5% of your service, for
example, if you take a policy of 10 lakhs,
then you can get your family health
checkup up to 5000 free of cost, friends,
which you get every year, friends,
apart from this, domiciliary hospital is also
covered in this policy, friends, that means if
you have any other problem, in any other region,
you have to get your treatment done at home, then that is also
covered up to the
injured, friends, that is also covered in this policy,
friends, apart from this, in this policy,
friends, you get restore benefit,
as we have already discussed in many policies
that you get restore benefit,
in this policy also you get 100%
restore benefit, what does it mean,
friends, but for example, you
take a policy of 10 lakhs and  If some of your
claims are made and some happen to him
then this policy will be automatically restored and if
you submit again then you
can take a claim of up to 10 lakhs again friends normally it has been
seen that this restore
benefit is not available in the policy but this feature has been
given by the company and if ever it
comes in the policy then you can make its benefit available
friends apart from this in this college
friends for animal pet you get a claim up to ₹ 10000
for which you do
not have to pay anything,
you can take a claim up to 10000 friends life long
is renewable friends in this if you
enter into this policy before 65
years then you
can renew this policy the company will not refuse you for any reason
friends so unlimited online OPD
is available friends this feature
is very good in this you can take online OPD
unlimited date is free of cost the company
gives you an app in which Hello Doctor  This
feature is available by the name of Up. You
can go online and lock your call there.
You
can consult with the doctor through voice call or video call for any kind
of OPD. This is the best feature in this
policy, friends, which you can avail.
Apart from this, there are some riders
like co-payment. If you feel
that your policy premium is getting
a bit high and you
want to reduce it, then you can reduce the policy premium by taking 10% or
20% co-payment rider.
Friends, I would advise you
not to take this rider because it does
not make much difference. By making a small difference,
you will have to pay a co-payment of 10%
or a co-payment of 20% in your claim.
It means that you have paid
₹2000 in premium, for example, but
if your claim is for ₹10 lakh, then either
₹1 lakh will be lost or ₹2 lakh will be lost.  If you have
taken it then do not take it,
but if you wish to, you can make this feature
available. Friends, apart from this,
friends, normally we have seen that what
happens is that there are some non-payable items
which people bought a lot during the time of Covid, but
their claim is not
received. So, there is a claim protector rider
feature available in this policy, which I would advise you to take
in this policy because its cost is nominal, it is not a
very high cost. If you
opt for that rider, then the type of non-
payable items will be reduced for you, but for example,
Glove Dettol, Cotton Pee Kid, all these are
such items whose cost will
not be reduced normally in policy, but by taking this claim
protector rider, all these non-payable
items will also be reduced, friends. So,
opt for this rider, this is my
advice to you. Friends, the premium of this policy
is understood with an illustration. Friends, in a
family floater policy, you have two children, husband, wife
with two children, 35 years of age, the
premium that is calculated on the average age.  10
lakh tax,
1912 friends, this is the premium of John 3,
apart from that the premium of John 2, the premium of John 1 will
increase a little, friends, so
you can check that premium at your location, the
rest we have given the details of the policy
in our description box, you can
go there and read all the terminal conditions of the policy,
friends, our number is
flashing on the screen,
apart from this we have put it in the Google form description box,
if you have any advice,
any query, then you can put it in the Google form,
our team will automatically
contact you, apart from this, if you
need any details, then you can put it in the comment box,
we will try,
thank you friends, thank you
[Music]